what's up everyone Chambers will do five
he was a very special video today and
boy you I got a juicy for you so
apparently the new Sonic game Sonic
Frontiers just came out and two people
who are five I just have one thing if
you're buying it then you need to stop
it now in the game there is this line of
quests that goes through the sock the
Hedgehog animated history and actually
you not Sonic is the only one absent for
the lineup Sonic Frontier more like
Sonic fails because in it there's a
quest where it's a reference to like
Avengers Sonic the Hedgehog and then
after it's sad I am and then as you all
know suck iron was the third song TV
show but no no they skipped right over
that and you know what they put in his
place
Sonic X more like Sonic sucks because it
[ __ ] sucks while I suck other
girlfriends always ignored why don't
they give us anything I mean I wasn't
gonna buy it anyway because I don't play
modern Sonic [ __ ] and if you do then
stop it be like me this is why we don't
get good things anymore he don't like
planet Earth now I know there is a
perfect perfectly Resort explanation but
I'm still [ __ ] pissed and the reason
is a lot of people don't know but Sega
does not have the rights to use Sonic
Underground or its property like
mannequin Sonia
because there was an actual interview
with one of the show Runners and Riders
and he specifically said if Sega ever
wanted to create more soccer content
they would have to like call up whoever
owns Mac and Sonia and basically dick
entertainment on soccer because Sega
gave them gave them a couple billion
dollars and hey cookie job go make some
like cool cartoons and they made soccer
in the doodle boss and all the other
good [ __ ] it went bankrupt and it was
sold to another company so in short if
they wanna use soccer they have to find
out who owns Sonya Matthew that's
basically it but that's not why we're
here we're here to say don't buy Sonic
Frontiers don't buy Sonic fails it's
gameplay is bad it's Graphics all bad
and God forbid the terrible music
Sonic Underground Music is a bob up in
this [ __ ]
have you ever listened to Sonic
underman's music it's so good and soft
motives does they even have bottle B no
bottleby how is that a Sonic the
Hedgehog game no actually you know we
got Sonic the Hedgehog you got this
green eye
tall like banana nose idiot
acting like Sonic the Hedgehog when he's
not he's shorter than that he's a he's a
fat ass who eats chili dogs
and gets [ __ ] in the ass bye-bye
Montclair I'm dressed it [ __ ]
Sonic is Bobby's [ __ ]
and don't get me stopped where is Manny
where is Sonia oh I know they don't be
they don't want to bring in Mack the
Hedgehog because they don't want people
to know that song their head up has a
brother that is green and manic man
exhale looks like a pilot plant
they don't want people to see that
because they know it's bad
but it's actually good
people think it's bad I don't I love
Sonic Underground I love everything that
comes with it I love manic
I love everything about Sonic
Underground
it's the good [ __ ]
Sonic Frontiers ain't oh no oh no no
that's that's bad I I don't even want I
can what you believe actually I did not
watch a single trailer I didn't watch
one gameplay video why because it's bad
I know it's bad I don't you don't gotta
show me it
we know we don't need to see it stop
showing it to me
stop trying to sell models off we don't
want it well it's like undergrad where
stock Underground
you guys are making me crazy up in this
[ __ ]
damn I got a [ __ ] [ __ ]
I'm tired of this
[ __ ] is better than Sonic fails
you hear me sorry Frontier more like
stockpiles we don't we don't want to
play that we don't even want to look at
it Sonic Underground
that's good that's the good stuff right
there
[ __ ]
Sonic Underground
is the is the the [ __ ] tits so Sega
if you're watching this I only have one
thing to say to you
soccer is good
[ __ ]